

https://jezpacito.github.io/portfolio-app/

# **Profile Info**

A motivated professional with two years of web development experience using the Laravel Framework for backend development with the skills of creating APIs and PHP Laravel Unit testing; and the foundations of utilizing React js as my front-end JavaScript library for developing user interfaces. And have prior experience with git version control seeking a position in a growth-oriented organization where I can use my skills to the benefit of the company while having the opportunity to expand my skills.

## **Skills**

Laravel

React JS

Laravel Unit Test

HTML & CSS

MySQL

GIT

## **Trainings**

Raspberry Pi Using Python Training

**Computer System Servicing** 

Professional Web Design Training

## Language

English  $\star \star \star \star \star$ Tagalog  $\star \star \star \star \star$ Bisaya  $\star \star \star \star \star$ 

# Jezreel Joy Gatmaitan

Software Engineer

**Phone** 

**Email** 

0995-295-8720 jezreelgatmaitan.wrk@gmail.com

**Address** 

VSM Heights, Brgy. San Isidro General Santos City Philippines

# **Experience**

#### FullStack Developer

April 2021 - Present

#### Codevidia I General Santos City

Develop a clientwise smart tool web application that manages the process of annulment cases with subscription management.

Technologies: React JS, Material UI, Metronic & Laravel Framework URL: https://home.clientwiseportal.com

#### Junior Web Developer

June 2020 - April 2021

#### Boxtypd I General Santos City

- Develop a Online platform where citizens all over Region 12 Philippines can access the services of the Department of Trade and Industry (DTI) such as sales promotion and others.
- Maintained Legna Care staff management web application that manages the hiring process of home care nursing in UK.

Technologies: React JS, Ant Design, Laravel Framework URL: https://r12services.dti.gov.ph/

Laravel Backend Developer

February - May 2022

#### Xiklab Digital I Part-time

Dealer Portal web app that is separate from the Honda website. It will have integrations with SAP via a custom API that will be developed by Client's SAP vendor.

## **Education**

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

2016 - 2020

Holy Triniry College of General Santos City

Secondary 2014 - 2015

Esperanza National High School of Sultan Kudarat